Where are meditations
number 15 and 16 again?
I used the same image in both meditations:
the two
husbands. That's what we
call a tool. There are
96 of these tools. If you
know them, then you're really intelligent. And one of them
is the two husbands.
Tactics: woman happy. No, why?
Because the husband is yelling at her. What does that mean?
I don't know if it should
lead to
Nick. Quite good. Shopping.com.com makes.
The husbands. I am the woman. You
are one of the husbands. These are my
three unruly children. The three there. I
am the woman.
I am a woman. Worked and I have
three unruly children, and almost like in real
life.
And then I also have a husband. I
work full-time because my husband
likes to watch football and he has no
interest in it. Anyway,
five days a week I take the
children to school before I
go to work,
and then I work eight or ten hours,
and maybe even 14 hours. And on
the way home I still have to
buy groceries. If a husband
watches football, of course not.  Hänni, so when
I get home I'm really tired,
exhausted.
He knows the story because of what happened
on Tuesday afternoon. My boss told
me
on Wednesday I have to start earlier. It would probably be
a Skype call with
the mass ex. We have in America and we
live in China.
I don't know why I have to make a
call in the middle of the night. It's
always the Chinese who have to get
up in the middle of the night,
but my boss tells me, "Do
n't forget, you have to be at eight instead of
nine." So on Tuesday afternoon,
I show my three children that
tomorrow Mom has to go to work.
So I want them to be dressed,
not for their lives,
from 6:30. Please have your
homework finished, have your shoes on,
and then I'll take you to
school earlier because I have to go to
work earlier. And they promise 11
heads, like they sewed, and the next
morning, and when she goes into the room
and is still ski jumping
up and down in bed, we unfortunately did
n't lose their debt to their school.
You can find them because they're somewhere.  A
little bit
and activist epic club he should be the one
since the dumbest children are at the very front
who has mom listened for the three children
maybe or not but mom hears herself
because when mom
listens to herself saying something bad,
she dances a bad seed
always mascom next week Monday Monday
is always the worst day
you are because work was his
long day
you took the children to school you went
to work worked long hours
I count everything saying something interesting
about bronze we make life
really hard when you come late
but also sit with shy to ask you to stay late in the
evenings
Ambos yelled at me you are
late up to 10 minutes late that made me
work three hours longer yesterday
I am only ten minutes late
they don't understand that he ultimately
always works longer and longer
afterwards I
bought groceries because my husband football
head but I am tired and all
I want
the reason why I have a husband the only reason
I have him because he is
not at work that he me
I love the feeling when he hugs me, that's why
I have a warning,
and then I look forward to the hug. You get
home late and open
the door at home. Idiot father and
your marriage, they say you have a huge
face. The husband is angry because he didn't have any
food because you were late and didn't
get any food.
The normal reaction is, you're the
idiot. Never past,
you are you, idiot. I'm not a huge
face, you are the huge face. That
's the normal reaction.
What happens when you hear that more often?
You hear it, plant seeds, and next
week I'll do it again because you
make him do it again. You created it, because
why did he yell at me? Because you
planted the seed last week.
So created it. In whose fault is it? It's
your fault. Bad news.
Every person who gets upset that you've ever
met got it from you.
Everyone,
most want to say 90 percent of the
people who upset me come from
me, but my ex-husband doesn't come from
me. He's so bad, so awful,
that's what he thinks.  Man, in reality,
this husband whose name is
Shopping, I think, I believe
very deeply, finds in it that I didn't
cause it, it's not my
fault.
You can take a deep breath, I have no power, I have no power,
I only
opened the door, and then I was told,
I don't know where it comes from, the
husband, not my fault,
the husband, not my fault, does he exist, does he
not exist? In Buddhism, we call this
no, that is a self-existing
thing, that is quite clear, that is the
thing that doesn't exist, and that is the
meaning of the illusion. It looks like a
lady, but he isn't there.
That is Maya, that is the revolution. Do
n't become mystical, there is nothing
mystical about it. Go to a tone, men, this
husband is Meyer, this marriage bond, does
he really appear, but
nothing exists. The husband,
I am not to blame, I did
nothing, this husband doesn't exist, has
never existed, will
exist for me, and cannot exist
because he doesn't come from you, and that is
impossible. That is the impossible husband,
the other one, not the
flea, the lousy husband who chooses
I caused it,
I planted it last week with
my three children. I planted the seed by hearing
my own words,
and next week
the seed in the picture will come out, it doesn't grow on
anything, body and mind, and that is
dependent arising. If he wanted to
use long, domain Buddhist words,
the seed opens, dependent
arising. But we can also simply
say, it comes from my arms, it comes
from me, is there one who exists? Yes, he exists.
He is dependent. It arises
until clarity, they come together. It doesn't exist, he doesn't exist anymore, it's not there.
That is empty. The
absence of this husband in the universe
is called empty. The presence of the
husband who comes from my name is
dependent arising. Until
you reach the 8th Buddhist level,
every person, the one you, a Christian, will consist of two, always, always
two men in the
room, in your kitchen, always two, because one
mind, because your mind still
creates the wrong one, but you know that he
isn't there. There are always two husbands in
the kitchen. And now the big, big
question:
if you get upset and  So to speak, no,
I'm not stupid. You're stupid
if you know you're stupid by planting
a new seed. You're stupid because of when
you get upset, when you get
angry about what, worthy of anger,
shopping or Nick,
of course, about shopping. Learn something, understand
that every time
you get upset or nervous or anxious
or worried in my whole
life, then you're getting angry, worrying,
or anxious about something that isn't
there. And all the wars in
World War II, 100 million people
died,
for example,
100 million people. These enemies
never existed. 100
million people died because
they blamed someone who didn't even exist,
but it killed these people. It's insane,
it's unbelievable. I understand now. What do
we call it when you say, "I know where
you're from," because I texted my children last week?
I would
n't have said it, my tone. What do we call it
when you use apprenticeship time to hold back your
anger?
That's true for me.  That's the definition
of the tub.
I won't get angry because
I know that with it I'm planting a new
company and that keeps
the cycle going. You have